<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OWASP Functions on quobix</title><link>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/</link><description>Recent content in OWASP Functions on quobix</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:33:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>owaspHeaderDefinition</title><link>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspheaderdefinition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:32:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspheaderdefinition/</guid><description>owaspHeaderDefinition will check that headers have been defined with the supplied headers.
How do I use this function? This function is configured by the following functionOptions.
NAME DESCRIPTION TYPE REQUIRED? headers An array of all the headers to check for []string yes Example ruleset configuration my-security-rule: description: Check for the following rate limiting headers. type: validation given: $ then: function: owaspHeaderDefinition functionOptions: headers: - X-RateLimit-Limit - RateLimit-Limit - RateLimit-Reset</description></item><item><title>owaspDefineErrorDefinition</title><link>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspdefineerrordefinition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:16:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspdefineerrordefinition/</guid><description>owaspDefineErrorDefinition will check that an error response of either 400, 422 or 4XX has been defined.
Example ruleset configuration my-security-rule: description: Make sure operation defines error responses type: validation given: $.paths..responses then: function: owaspDefineErrorDefinition Used by the following rules:
owasp-define-error-validation owasp-define-error-responses-401 owasp-define-error-responses-500</description></item><item><title>owaspCheckSecurity</title><link>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspchecksecurity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:34:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://quobix.com/vacuum/functions/owasp/owaspchecksecurity/</guid><description>owaspCheckSecurity will check global or operation level security has been defined.
How do I use this function? This function is configured by the following functionOptions.
NAME DESCRIPTION TYPE REQUIRED? schemesPath The key to look for (defaults to securitySchemes) []string yes nullable Can be empty or not boolean yes methods Which http methods to look through []string yes Example ruleset configuration my-security-rule: description: API should be protected by a `security` rule either at global or operation level.</description></item></channel></rss>